In this shooting game, there are two modes of playing:
•	Single Player mode – in which there is one player playing against all the enemies. The controls for the Single Player mode are simple:  the user uses the arrows (Left, Right, Up and Down) to control the movement of the player on the screen; the user uses the Left-CTRL key to shoot bullets. The player has 5 lives and the game is over when the player loses all his lives, or when he defeats the Fortress. A life is lost when the Player’s health reaches 0%. At this point, if the Player has more lives the current level will be restarted.
•	Multiplayer mode – in which there are two player instances, both controlled from the same keyboard. The controls for the first Player are the same as in Single Player mode and the controllers for the second Player are: the user uses W-key to go up, S-key to go down, A-key to go left and D-key to go right; the user uses the Left-SHIFT key to shoot bullets. In this mode both Players have 5 lives each and the game is over when either one of the Players runs out of lives, or when the Fortress is killed. If either one of the Players runs out of health, he will lose a life and the current level will be restarted if he still has more lives.
